OK, remember that when you are sitting in a stool it's a little bit different than sitting in a chair on the floor.
So what I want you to do is once again think about your legs ladies.
Keep the knees together.
Keep the legs crossed.
Ladies keep in mind I keep my right foot in front.
I place my left foot behind the right and then I place it on the step of the stool.
Resting the legs this feels much more comfortable than dangling or them with the knees apart.
Which is very unattractive as we know.
So keep your hands again to the side.
Keep your posture maintain it and in a stool your going to find you're going to sit a little bit deeper into the seat of the chair.
Than you do a chair on the floor because your feet are now lifted from the floor.
So you're unable to keep that security with your feet on the floor.
This is why you want to keep the right foot in front.
The left one behind and a little bit of placement with the feet diagonal.
On the right side of the chair here.
While I rest my hands on the left hip.
So it gives your body balance and a lot of security while sitting high up in a stool.
Which is raised up off the floor.